<node id="AllYours">
	<body>
		<p>You walk down the hallway. It takes a couple of turns and ends, predictably, at a door. On the door is written the words, THE END. You step through.
		</p>
		
		<p>The next room is nothing like the others. It has a carpet, a window overlooking a forest, a comfy-looking couch, and a small stove in the corner. A woman stands at the stove, cooking something that smells wonderful.
		</p>
		
		<p data-if="FavoriteFood == 'pancakes'">“Hello [$Name$],” she says. “I made you pancakes. Your favorite.” She flips a pancake off the stove and onto a plate, which she hands to you. “Please, sit and eat.” You sit on the couch and take a bite of the pancake – light and fluffy, just the way you like it.</p>

		<p data-if="FavoriteFood == 'oatmeal'"> “Hello [$Name$],” she says. “I made you oatmeal. Your favorite.” She dips a ladle into a pot on the stove and empties it into a bowl, which she hands to you. “Please, sit and eat.” You sit on the couch and take a bite – a touch of cinnamon, just the way you like it.</p> 

		<p data-if="FavoriteFood == 'bacon'">“Hello [$Name$],” she says. “I made you bacon. Your favorite.” She slides a couple of pieces onto a plate, which she hands to you. “Please, sit and eat.” You sit on the couch and take a bite – a tiny bit burnt, just the way you like it.</p>

		<p>“[$Name$],” she says, “I’ve been waiting for you for a long time. You chose to come in, you passed the challenge, and now I know that you’re the one.”</p>

		<p>“The one for what?” you ask.</p>

		<p>“I built this place,” she says, “and I’ve been running it for almost 50 years. It’s my life’s work. But now, I’m tired. I’m looking for someone to take over. And that someone is you.”</p>

		<p>“Me?”</p>

		<p>“That’s right. You can bring new people here. Let them go through the rooms and the doors and the challenges. Or you can shut the place down. It’s all up to you.”</p>

		<p>She sees your confused expression and smiles kindly. “Right now,” she says, “go ahead and finish your [$FavoriteFood$]. Then you can decide what to do next.”</p>

		<center>
			<img src="the_end.png" />	
			<br />
			<div data-type="reset" />
		</center>
	</body>
</node>